const questions = [
	{
		question: "What is the full meaning HTML",
		options: [
			{ opt: "High Text Mosaic Language" },
			{ opt: "Hyper Text Markup Language" },
			{ opt: "An english language" },
			{ opt: "A language" },
		],
		correct: "Hyper Text Markup Language",
		id: 1,
	},
	{
		question: "What is Javascript",
		options: [
			{ opt: "A scripting language" },
			{ opt: "A markup language" },
			{ opt: "An english language" },
			{ opt: "A language" },
		],
		correct: "A scripting language",
		id: 2,
	},
	{
		question: "Which year was Node.js released?",
		options: [
			{ opt: "2010" },
			{ opt: "2016" },
			{ opt: "2009" },
			{ opt: "2004" },
		],
		correct: "2009",
		id: 3,
	},
	{
		question: "What is || in Javascript",
		options: [
			{ opt: "and" },
			{ opt: "either" },
			{ opt: "with" },
			{ opt: "or" },
		],
		correct: "or",
		id: 4,
	},
	{
		question: "What is the full meaning of NPM?",
		options: [
			{ opt: "Node Package Manager" },
			{ opt: "Nano Particle Motion" },
			{ opt: "Node Plugin Manager" },
			{ opt: "Node Package Mongo" },
		],
		correct: "Node Package Manager",
		id: 5,
	},
	{
		question: "The following are asynchronous programming concepts except",
		options: [
			{ opt: "callbacks" },
			{ opt: "fufil" },
			{ opt: "Promises" },
			{ opt: "async/await" },
		],
		correct: "Fufil",
		id: 6,
	},
	{
		question:
			"In an ecosystem the transformation of energy is brought about by",
		options: [
			{ opt: "machine" },
			{ opt: "sunlight" },
			{ opt: "activities of living things" },
			{ opt: "heat energy" },
		],
		correct: "activities of living things",
		id: 7,
	},
	{
		question: "Food gives energy",
		options: [{ opt: "yes" }, { opt: "no" }],
		correct: "yes",
		id: 8,
	},
	{
		question: "Which of the following is a class of food",
		options: [
			{ opt: "beans" },
			{ opt: "yam" },
			{ opt: "protein" },
			{ opt: "kitchen" },
		],
		correct: "protein",
		id: 9,
	},

	{
		question: "How many bones does an average human being have ",
		options: [{ opt: "205" }, { opt: "100" }, { opt: "206" }, { opt: "207" }],
		correct: "206",
		id: 10,
	},
	{
		question: "What is the strongest muscle in the human body ",
		options: [
			{ opt: "biseps" },
			{ opt: "trisep" },
			{ opt: "mantissa" },
			{ opt: "tendon" },
		],
		correct: "mantissa",
		id: 11,
	},
	{
		question: "What type of protein is found in the curticles ",
		options: [
			{ opt: "beans" },
			{ opt: "milk" },
			{ opt: "chitin" },
			{ opt: "hydroelastic" },
		],
		correct: "chitin",
		id: 12,
	},
	{
		question: "There are three forms of skeleton ",
		options: [{ opt: "yes" }, { opt: "no" }, { opt: "maybe" }, { opt: "idk" }],
		correct: "yes",
		id: 13,
	},
	{
		question: "What is the component of a basic ecosystem ",
		options: [
			{ opt: "enviroment" },
			{ opt: "habitat" },
			{ opt: "objects" },
			{ opt: "a and b" },
		],
		correct: "a and b",
		id: 14,
	},
	{
		question: "An enzyme is made up of ",
		options: [
			{ opt: "chemical" },
			{ opt: "protein" },
			{ opt: "hydrostatic energy" },
			{ opt: "carborhydrate" },
		],
		correct: "protein",
		id: 15,
	},
];
export default questions;
